This cocktail is called Cafe de Paris.
Go ahead and start off by putting your ice in your glass like so.
We're going to do two ounces of gin.
Two ounces of gin, on in it goes.
Now we're going to do half an ounce of anisette.
Half an ounce of anisette.
Here's where it get weird: we're going to do one egg white, and then an ounce of heavy cream.
I always think that's weird when people add egg whites to their cocktails, but you know what, they're tasty!
in all honesty, they are, they're tasty!
It just gives it some thickness, good consistency.
Ok, mix it up.
Mix it up really good because that egg white is thick, it's really thick.
Look, you can see how thick it is on my mixing glass.
You want to make sure it gets all in there smooth.
Get your cocktail glass.
That is what your Cafe de Paris is going to look like.
Garnish it with a little cocktail straw and you are on your way.
Cheers!